《反恐24小时》前情提要
Previously on 24
我是肯·德奥  CNB的记者
Ken Dellao,CNB.
我想跟您确认一条信息
I'm wondering if you can confirm some information.
我想在今晚的报道中播报
I'm gonna be reporting in this evening's broadcast
一名叫杰克·鲍尔的前联邦探员
that a rogue ex-federal agent named Jack Bauer
涉嫌谋杀了莱恩·伯内特
is the prime suspect in the murder of Ryan Burnett.
你把伯内特被杀的消息
You leaked this story of Burnett's murder
还有我的介入都透露给了媒体
and my involvement to the press.
那么你又一次的失策
So another one of your errors in
让你搬起石头砸了自己的脚
judgment bites you on the ass.
你这一次玩得过火了
You've gone too far this time.
蕾妮  我是杰克  拜托别挂电话
Renee,it's Jack. Don't hang up the phone,please.
不论他们怎么说  我没杀伯内特
Whatever they told you,I did not kill Burnett.
我把真凶的照片发给你了
I sent you a photo of the man who did.
我只是想让你查明他的身份
All I want you to do is make an ID.
约翰·奎恩  参与秘密行动的退伍老兵
John Quinn,Black Ops combat vet.
现在为斯塔克伍德公司卖命
He works for Starkwood.
斯塔克伍德和朱玛是一伙的吗
Starkwood work with Juma?
即使是  也根本无案可查
If they did,it wasn't on the books.
但若有人知情  就一定是迈尔参议员
You know,if anyone knows,it's senator Mayer.
蕾妮  鲍尔在哪
Renee,where's Bauer?
-不知道  -别骗我
- I don't know. - Don't you lie to me.
我们知道你进入了政府机密数据库
We know you accessed a classified government database
把某人的姓名和地址发给了鲍尔
and sent someone's name and address to Bauer.
告诉我他在哪
Tell me where he is.
我办不到
I can't.
把她关起来
Put her in holding.
告知她应享有的权利
Mirandize her.
如果鲍尔把我们和朱玛联系起来的话
If Bauer connects us to Juma,
这次行动就会严重受阻
it could seriously impede this operation.
是的  没错
Yes,it could.
货能按时送到吗
Is the shipment on time?
能  一个小时内到港
Yes. Due into port in the next hour.
一旦武器部署完毕
Once the weapons are deployed,
鲍尔或是其他人知不知道都无所谓了
then it doesn't matter what Mr. Bauer or anyone else knows.
我没杀伯内特
I didn't kill Burnett.
是这个家伙杀的
This man did.
他叫约翰·奎恩
His name is John Quinn.
他为斯塔克伍德卖命
He works for Starkwood.
那斯塔克伍德和这一切有什么关联
And what does Starkwood have to do with this?
你的线人声称斯塔克伍德企图
Your informant claims that Starkwood was trying
获得生化武器  这就能联系上朱玛了
to acquire a bioweapon,and that's your connection to Juma.
你在过去这半年来一直在试图
You've been trying to dismantle Starkwood
解散斯塔克伍德公司
for the last six months.
他们要是有这种武器
If they have a weapon like this,
你最好相信他们有使用它的企图
you better believe they intend to use it.
不要
No!
告诉我那些武器会从哪里入境
Just tell me where the weapons are coming in.
太迟了
You're too late.
武器已经运到了
They're already here.
以下情节发生在晚间10点至11点间
The following takes place between 10 p.m. and 11 p.m.
长官
Sir?
对现场的初步调查已经结束
Preliminary sweep of the immediate area's done.
没有鲍尔的踪迹
There's no sign of Bauer.
好吧  扩大搜捕范围
All right,widen the grid.
还得去查看封锁线周边的摄像监控
And run down security cameras around the perimeter
-一定有人看到了他  -是  长官
- Witness or somebody must have seen him.  - Yes,sir.
卡宁先生
Mr.Kanin?
请讲
Yes?
拉里·莫斯想和您通话
Larry Moss is on the line.
莫斯探员
Agent Moss,
拜托告诉我你已经拘禁了杰克·鲍尔
please tell me you have Jack Bauer in custody.
我也希望如此  卡宁先生  但事实是
I wish that were the case,Mr. Kanin,but the truth is...
先生  是参议员迈尔
Sir,it's senator Mayer.
他遇害了
He's dead.
什么
What?!
他在自己家中被杀了
He was murdered at his house.
我们只发现了鲍尔刚才来过这里
We only found out that Bauer was on his way over here a short time ago.
不幸的是  我们来迟了一步
Unfortunately,we got here too late.
等等
Wait a minute.
你是说
Are you telling me
杰克·鲍尔杀了一位美国议员吗
that jack bauer just killed a United States senator?
这只是假设  我们仍在调查  先生
That's the assumption that we're working under,yes,Sir.
你们怎么能让这种事发生  莫斯探员
How could you have let this happen，Agent Moss?!
他耍了我们所有人  先生
He had us all fooled,sir.
我把杰克·鲍尔交由你看管
I released Jack Bauer into your custody!
我叫你看紧点儿他
I ordered you to keep him on a short leash!
不  卡宁先生  你别把这一切
No,no. Mr. Kanin,you are not
都怪在我头上
gonna lay this one on my feet.
是你同意让鲍尔审问伯内特的
It was your decision to give Bauer access to Burnett.
当时我还反对来着
I advised you against it.
卡宁先生
Mr. Kanin?
抱歉
I'm sorry. Uh,
你刚说什么来着
What did you say?
我刚说  当时我还反对来着
I said,I advised you against it.
是的  你说过
Yes, you did.
先生  我的人还在搜查该区域
Sir,I have teams sweeping the area.
找到他  莫斯探员
Just find him,Agent Moss.
是  我会的
Yeah,I will.
斯塔克伍德和今天发生的一切都有关联
Starkwood was involved with everything that happened today.
是他们协助朱玛一伙
They were the ones that helped Juma and his men
撞毁飞机并袭击白宫
bring down those planes and attack the White House.
作为交换  他们获准在桑加拉
In exchange,they were allowed to develop
研发并生产大规模杀伤性武器
and manufacture a WMD in Sangala.
是种生化武器
It's a bioweapon.
显然  这种武器现在已在美国
Apparently,it's already here in the U.S.
还有谁知道这些
Who else knows about this?
没了  迈尔参议员和我
No one. Senator Mayer and I
正在对这些信息抽丝剥茧
were piecing together the information
然后他就被杀了
right before he was killed.
你说武器已经在这儿了
You said the weapon's already here.
已经在他们手上了吗
Are they in possession of it?
应该还没有  我从他们手下的手机里
I don't think so. The text message I got
获取的短信显示
off their agent's cell phone said,
亚历山大港  下午3点
"port of alexandria,15 p.m."
我们为什么不把这事报告给调查局
Why don't we just call the FBI
让他们封锁整个地区
and lock the whole place down?
咱俩可都是逃犯  托尼
Because we're fugitives,Tony.
谁会信咱们
No one's going to believe us.
咱得先查明那批武器的确切位置
We need to know exactly where that weapon is
然后才能通知他们赶来
before we call anyone else in.
托尼  你得告诉我你是否愿意跟我干
Tony,I need to know if you're with me on this.
好吧  我跟你干
Yeah,I'm with you.
好  我们在港口北端见
Okay. Meet me at the north end of the port.
从主入口前面那条路进来
There's an access road right before the main entrance.
好  我马上就到
All right,I'll be there.
都结束了
It's over.
杜巴库和朱玛都死了
Dubaku and Juma are dead.
那些发动恐怖袭击的人
Everyone responsible for the terrorist attacks...
还有害死我儿罗杰的恶贼都被一网打尽
responsible for Roger.
感谢上帝
Thank god for that.
还有  还有些事
And there's... there's something else.
不幸中的万幸
Something good that's come out of all of this.
奥利维亚和我都在白宫
Olivia is here at the white house.
奥利维亚
Olivia?
她回到我们身边了  亨利
She's come home,Henry.
这场危机让咱一家再次凝聚在了一起
The crisis-- it brought us together.
我已让她留下做特别顾问了
I've asked her to stay on as special advisor,and-and
她也答应了
She's agreed.
艾莉
Ally...
我都说不出  有多开心
I can't begin to tell you how happy that makes me.
我也是
Me,too.
亲爱的  我知道你累了
Sweetheart,i know that you're tired.
好好休息吧
You should get some rest.
只要一有时间
Olivia and i will come to the hospital
奥利维亚和我会去医院看你的
Just as soon as we can.
好啊
When you can.
我哪儿也不去  在这等你们
I'm not going anywhere.
告诉奥利维亚我爱她
Give Olivia my love.
我爱你
Love you.
我们也爱你
We love you,too.
医生说他可以完全康复的
The doctors expect him to make a full recovery.
亨利比我们想象的  要坚强得多
Henry's a lot tougher than anyone thought.
希望如此  希望如此
Oh,maybe,maybe,maybe,just maybe,
希望结局会皆大欢喜
This day will end on a positive note.
怎么了  伊桑  出什么事了
What is it,ethan? what's wrong?
很遗憾地告知您  总统阁下
I'm sorry to have to tell you this,madam president,
迈尔参议员死了
But senator mayer is dead.
怎么回事
What happened?
所有证据都表明
All evidence points to the fact that he was murdered
他是被杰克·鲍尔谋杀的
By jack bauer.
鲍尔
Bauer?
我知道这让人难以置信
It's hard to believe,i know.
说不通啊
It-it doesn't make any sense.
今天他为我们立下汗马功劳
After everything He has done today,
怎么还会杀迈尔参议员呢
Why on earth would he do this?
找到他  就会真相大白了
We'll know more when we find him.
天哪
My god.
总统阁下
Madam president,
鉴于所发生的一切
In light of what's happened,
为了维护您本届政府的利益
And for the sake of your administration,
恐怕我只能辞去联席参谋长一职了
I'm afraid i have no choice but to resign as your chief of staff.
伊桑
Ethan!
总统阁下  您听我说
Madam president,please,you need to hear this.
是我下令解禁鲍尔
Inevitably,it'll come to light that i sanctioned
不可避免  此事终究会被曝光的
Bauer's release from custody.
除非我立即辞职
Unless i step down immediately,
否则这对您的政府和您个人
The damage to your office,and you personally,
都将会造成巨大的伤害
Will be extensive.
伊桑  奥利维亚今天已封锁了这个消息
Ethan,Olivia has already killed this story once today.
我们可以控制事态蔓延
We can control the damage.
不
No.
现在就算是奥利维亚也无能为力
No,not even Olivia can control it now.
参议员被谋杀之后就不可能了
Not after the senator's murder.
总统阁下  事实上
The truth is,madam president,
我没能竭尽所能地保护您
I didn't do enough to protect you.
事实是  我辜负了您
The truth is,i failed you.
我应该为这些后果负责
And i should shoulder the blame for what's happened.
伊桑  说真的  你
Ethan,really,you're...
你想的太多了
You're taking this too far.
是吗
Am i?
我不确定
I'm not so sure.
因为您女儿曾经非常明确地表明
As your daughter has made abundantly clear,
我对此事负有不可推卸的责任
I have a lot to answer for.
对我而言  你只是一名优秀的顾问
You have done nothing but be an invaluable advisor to me
更是我的好友
And an even better friend.
总统阁下  很感激您能这么说
I appreciate you saying that,Madam president,
但是奥利维亚是对的
but Olivia's right.
早晚会有人借此兴风作浪
The political knives will be out.
我所做出的每个决定将会被审查
Every decision i've made will be scrutinized.
将由独立检察官介入此事
There will be calls for a special prosecutor.
您是位伟大的女性  艾莉森
You're a great woman,Allison.
还有未竟的伟业要您去完成
You have great work yet to do.
我现在是您的累赘
I'm a liability to you now.
别让我成为您今后三年政治生涯的绊脚石
Don't let me compromise your next three years in office.
别让我拖累您的工作
Don't let me sink your agenda.
是我们的工作  伊桑
Our agenda,ethan.
对啊
Yes.
我们的工作
Our agenda.
相信我  总统阁下
Trust me,madam president,
这么做没错
It's the right thing to do.
请接受我的辞职
Accept my resignation.
明早我会递交辞呈
I'll have a letter on your desk in the morning.
他们随时会到
They're gonna be here any minute.
我们得缩小搜索范围
We need to narrow down the search.
如果他们今天卸货  货应该还在码头
If they offloaded it today, It should still be on the storage dock.
杰克  那照样是大海捞针
That's still a needle in a haystack,jack.
那边有上千个集装箱
There must be over a thousand containers in there.
我们得拿到那里的载货单
We need to access the yard's manifest.
那边安保措施怎么样
What's the security?
-我发现了一个港务局警察  -就一个人
- I've spotted one port authority officer. - That's it?
就一个人
That's it.
应该还有其他人
There's got to be more.
走
Come on,let's go.
亲爱的  不会有事的
Honey,it'll be fine.
再过几小时就有人来换班了
I get relieved in a few hours.
卡尔  你知道我不愿让你连上两个班
Carl,you know i don't like you working double shifts.
是我自己选的嘛
Well,it was my choice.
更何况  加班费可以补贴家用
And we could use the overtime.
女儿们怎么样
How are the girls?
整晚在我肚子里乱踢呢
Kicking like a chorus line tonight.
她们都想爸爸了
They miss their daddy.
医生怎么说
What'd the doctor say?
还好我怀的不是三胞胎
That i'm lucky it's not triplets.
亲爱的  我再打给你
Honey,let me call you back.
别想拿枪
Don't even think about going for your weapon.
我要港口的卸货单  在哪儿
I need the port's manifest. where is it?
我只是个港务局警察
I am just the p.a. cop
在哪儿
Where is it?
在海关
Customs house.
那边
That way.
走
Let's go.
准时到了吗
We're on schedule?
我们正在靠近港口的集结地  先生
We're at the staging area near the port,sir,
不过我们还在等奎恩
but we're still waiting on Quinn.
他现在应该已经到了
He should have been there by now.
有他的消息吗
Have you heard from him?
给他打了电话  但是没人接
We've tried his cell,but he's not answering.
如果鲍尔杀了奎恩
If Bauer took out Quinn,
他就有可能知道了这次行动
He might have knowledge of the operation.
对吗
Mightn't he?
要我们撤退吗  先生
Should we stand down,sir?
不  再等奎恩5分钟
No. give Quinn five more minutes,
到时再行动
Then go in.
要极其谨慎行事
Do so with extreme caution
等你们把集装箱拿到手之后
Then contact me the minute
马上联系我
That you've secured the container.
是的  先生
Yes,sir.
董事会成员都到了  先生
Everybody on the board is here,sir.
你愁容满面的  格雷格
You have a worried look,Greg.
气氛很紧张  先生
It's very tense in there,sir.
他们好对付  格雷格
They're six-year-olds,Greg.
只要有的吃就好
And they need to eat their carrots.
道格
Doug
漫长的一天  对美国来说真是漫长的一天
Rough day. A rough day for the United States of America.
白宫遇袭被围
The White House under siege,
总统被劫持为人质
The president taken hostage...
尤其痛苦的是
It's especially painful
我们知道这一切本没必要发生
Because we know this didn't have to be.
事实上  美国军队
In fact, the United States Military
已经到了崩溃的边缘
Is strained to the breaking point.
事实上  恢复公司职能的草案
In fact, Reinstatement of the draft
也因为政治原因不予讨论
Is off the table for political reasons.
事实上  这间屋里坐着的人
In fact, the people in this room,
你们都掌控着西半球最大的私人军队
you all control the largest private army in the western hemisphere.
那么  难道我们今天没有用武之地了吗
Now,could we have been of help today?
我们当然有用武之地的
You bet your ass we could've been of help!
但他们并没有找我们  是吧
But they didn't call us,did they?
相反
No. instead,
我们坐着无所事事  我们的合同被取消了
We sit here,our contracts are canceled,
我们的士兵被无视  我们的公司主权
Our soldiers' vilified,our corporate sovereignty
也受到了国会法令的威胁
Is threatened by congressional fiat.
道格  是你牵头与政府签订了协议
Doug,you brokered the deal with this government.
但你目光短浅
You were short-sighted
政府并不明白  全球反恐战争
And they don't understand that the global war
只能依靠我们这样的部队来取得胜利
On terror can only be won by forces like ours.
所以从现在开始
So as of this minute,we sit
我们不再提供证词
For no more depositions.
我们不再提供相关文件
We volunteer no more documents.
甚至  我不想让你们接听电话
I don't even want us to take any phone calls.
你叫我们来就是想要说这个
Is that what this is about?
-为了国家的安全  -你就是想说这个
- With the security of our country,  - Is that what this is about?
我们可承受不了公司被他们搞垮的风险
We cannot afford to let them take us down.
你就是想说这个
Is that what this is about then?
你来这里
You came here
叫董事们冒着被联邦政府起诉的风险
To ask the board to risk a federal indictment?
你这样不行的  乔纳斯
It won't work,Jonas.
我们和政府达成了协议
We got a deal.
这协议不错  对我们来说是幸事
It's a good deal and we're lucky to have it.
跟想要毁掉我们的政府达成协议
With an administration that wants to destroy us.
跟想要整垮我们的政府达成协议
Wants to take us out of business.
不行  今时不同往日
No,it's all different now.
是时候改变一下游戏规则了
Today was a game-changer.
不行  从制度上来说
No,institutionally,
我们要按传票上说的做
We are in compliance with the subpoena.
文件也上交了
Documents have been filed,
证词也录过了
Depositions taken.
不再这样做了
Not anymore.
乔纳斯  我们必须跟政府合作
Jonas,we have to stay engaged with this administration.
不  道格
no,we don't,Doug.
此事我们可以通过商谈消除分歧
You and i can talk this out.
如果大家还有其他问题
If you guys have any questions,any further questions,
格雷格  你留在这里回答他们的问题
Greg,you will stick around and you'll answer them.
谢谢各位
Thank you.
谢谢
道格  你这样做不对的
Your way was a mistake,Doug.
你必须承认这点
You have to acknowledge that.
也许吧  但你我都知道
Maybe. but you and i both know
斯塔克伍德若全力反对小组委员会
That starkwood cannot survive
是没好果子吃的
An all-out war against the subcommittee.
这个  我来操心好了
Let me worry about that.
不  你应该操心的是参议员迈尔
No,you should worry about senator Mayer.
他是不会善罢甘休的
He's not going to let go of this.
他紧咬着不放
He's got his teeth in it.
迈尔参议员已经死了
Senator Mayer's dead.
很不幸  就在近一个小时前
He was killed by a rogue federal agent
他被一个身为联邦探员的无赖杀死了
Not one hour ago,tragically.
乔纳斯
Jonas.
告诉我你跟这件事没关系
Tell me you had nothing to do with this.
你是在指责我  合谋参与了
Are you accusing me of complicity
迈尔参议员的谋杀吗
In the murder of senator mayer?
我要你亲口告诉我
I want a personal assurance.
政治暗杀可不是斯塔克伍德的业务  道格
Starkwood is not in the business of political assassination,Doug.
但或许我们可以研究研究
Though maybe we should look into it.
听说干这一行前景不错
I hear it's a growth market.
杰克  你有什么发现
Jack,you finding anything?
今天有12条船在这里卸货
12 ships were unloaded here today.
有从桑加拉来的吗
Any from sangala?
西非那里可没有深水港
There's no deepwater port in that area of West Africa.
如果武器是从那里来的
If the weapon originated from there,
必须经陆路运到刚果港口城市黑角
It would've had to overland into Pointe-Noire.
就是那个港口  [刚果  黑角港口]
Where...  [Port of Pointe-Noire-Congo]
在过去4周里  这12条船中有2条
Two of the 12 ships acquired
从那个港口接过货
Cargo from that port within the last four weeks.
快点
Come on.
快点  该死  [核实用户名和密码]
Come on. damn it!  [Username & Password Validation]
-怎么了  -我无法获取他们的载货单
- What is it? - I can't access their manifests
数据库有密码保护
their database is password protected.
警官  怎么称呼
What's your name,officer?
盖森
Gadsen.
卡尔·盖森
Carl gadsen.
关于密码  我什么都不知道
I don't have any information about a password.
卡尔  你仔细听我说
Carl,i want you to listen to me very carefully.
今早策划两架飞机相撞
The same terrorists who took down two planes earlier today
和袭击白宫的恐怖分子
And attacked the White House are trying
正试图获得大规模杀伤性武器
To acquire a weapon of mass destruction.
他们马上就要来拿那些武器了
They're coming here to pick up that weapon.
武器就装在外面码头的某个集装箱里
It's somewhere out there in your yard in one of those canisters.
听着  我知道这或许让你难以相信
Look,i understand this might be hard for you to believe.
不  实际上不无可能
No,actually,it's not.
你时间不多了
You don't have a lot of time.
此话怎讲
What do you mean?
他们是要来
They are coming.
事实上  他们应该已经到了
In fact,they should be here already.
继续说  卡尔
Keep talking,Carl.
他们告诉我
They told me they were smuggling in
他们从南韩走私过来一批电子产品
Electronics from South Korea.
我发誓
I swear.
我完全不知道他们是恐怖分子
I had no idea they were terrorists.
那你答应帮他们做什么
What'd you agree to do for them?
打开前门  就当什么都没看见
Open the front gate. look the other way.
仅仅这样吗
Is that it?
关闭监视器
Disable the security cameras.
这么大的场地应该有更多的警员看守
A yard this size should have more police officers.
-他们在哪里  -我是这里的主管
- Where are they? - I'm the supervisor.
轮班是我安排的
I do the shift schedules.
我支开了所有人
I made sure i'd be the only one here.
知道这个就足够了
That's enough confirmation for me.
我去打电话  你来给他松绑
I'm making the call. untie him.
他给谁打电话
Who's he calling?
联邦调查局  既然现在我们确认
The FBI. now that we're confident
武器就在这里  我们就要通知当局了
The weapon's here,we're calling in the authorities.
托尼  我电话用不了  座机也是
Tony? my cell is down,so is the landline.
有人在干扰通信
Someone's jamming communications.
卡尔  回答
Carl, pick up
是他们
It's them.
那个对讲机是他们给的  说会联系我
They gave me that radio; told me they'd be contacting me.
回答他们  尽量跟他们合作
answer the call. just play along.
卡尔
Carl
回答他们
Answer the call.
我还以为你们不会来了呢
I didn't think you were coming.
-你们来晚了  -现在不是来了吗
- You're late. - Well,we're here now
正等着呢
And we're waiting.
好吧
Okay.
他们在大门那边
They're at the front gate.
把皮带系上
Put your belt back on.
我要你回到岗位上
I want you to resume your post.
假装若无其事
Pretend like everything's normal.
-把他们放进来  -然后呢
- Just let them in. - And then what?
他们一拿到集装箱  我们就会跟踪他们
We're going to follow them as soon as they pick up
一旦过了信号屏蔽区
Their container; once we're past
-我们就会打电话给当局  -我不确定
- The jamming grid,we'll make our call. -I don't know.
什么叫你不确定
What do you mean you don't know?
你脱不了干系  卡尔
You're a part of this,Carl,
这可由不得你
Whether you want to be or not.
当你答应他们的时候
You became a part of it this the second you said
-你就已经上了贼船了  -杰克
- "yes" to these people. - Jack!
-看见什么了  -看见三辆车
- What do you got? - I got three vehicles.
8个敌人
Eight hostiles,
全副武装  估计车里还有更多人
Heavily armed; got to assume there's more inside the trucks.
卡尔  如果你不开门
Carl,if you don't open that gate,they're going
他们肯定会闯进来抓你  懂吗
To come in here looking for you,you understand me?
我这么跟你说吧
Let me put it to you this way.
这些人今天已经杀了300多人了
These men have killed over 300 people today.
如果他们拿到这些武器
If they get a hold of that weapon,
再去杀人就易如反掌
They're going to make that look like child's play.
你别无选择
You've only got one choice here.
我只要开门把他们放进来
I just open the gate and let them in.
你做这些就够了
That's all you've got to do.
-你们会保护我  对吗  -是的
- And you guys got my back,right?  - Yeah.
向我保证
Promise me.
我向你保证
I promise you.
好吧
Okay.
托尼  把监听装置拿过来
Tony,get the surveillance package.
别担心
Don't worry.
这样我们就能听监听实况
It's just so we can hear what's going on.
转过来
Turn around.
我得把这个放在你背后
I need to put this on your back.
听着  关于那些钱
Listen,the money-- it wasn't about
不是因为我贪财
Greed or anything.
只是我妻子  琳达  她要生双胞胎了
It's my wife,Linda. she's having twins.
这是最天经地义的事了  对吗
They say it's the most natural thing in the world,right?
怀孕
Getting pregnant?
我们花了三年时间
Well,it took us three years,
付出了太多的代价
Cost an arm and a leg.
我不是找借口  但生育保险费简直太少了
No excuses,but insurance doesn't cover a dime.
我只是太想有个完整的家庭
I just always wanted to have a family.
你们能理解吗
You know what i mean?
把这个揣进口袋
Put this in your pocket.
能收到吗
You got him?
能
Yeah.
记住  就把这当成跟平常上班一样
Remember,it's just another day at the office.
你不会有事的
You're going to be fine.
走吧
Let's go.
卡尔  你怎么才来
What took you so long,Carl?
带了通行文件了吗
You got the routing documents?
当然
Sure.
我得看一下 以确定集装箱的位置
I need to see them in order to locate the container.
行了  卡尔  就在这儿呢
Relax,Carl. they're right here.
好吧
Okay.
中部
Center section.
36排Q区
Row 36,Q-block.
就在你右手边的第四个货堆里面
It's that fourth stack on your right.
我知道集装箱在哪  卡尔
I know where the container is,Carl.
你把监控摄像头都关了吗
Did you disable the security cameras?
只留了10点钟方向的那个
um,all but one else on 10 o'clock,
照你说的做了
Just like you said.
你妻子还好吧
How's your wife?
她很好
She's fine.
你没告诉她这件事  是吧
You didn't tell her anything about this,did you?
没有  当然没有
No,of course not.
你还告诉过别人吗
Did you tell anybody else?
没有  我干嘛要告诉别人呢
No,no,why would i?
你说呢  卡尔
You tell me,Carl.
你怎么突然这么紧张了呢
Why are you so nervous?
好吧  你想知道真相是吧  斯多克斯
Okay,um,you want to know the truth,Mr. Stokes?
我以为你们就是单纯过来取东西
Uh... i was expecting a simple pickup,
但是看见你
But you show up
-带着这么多人过来  然后  -然后怎样
- With a small army here,and,um... - And what?
只是  出乎我的意料  仅此而已
It's just... not w-what i was expecting,that's all.
我只是不想被抓到
I just don't want to get caught.
没人会被抓到的 卡尔
Nobody's gonna get caught,Carl.
走吧  出发
Let's go,we're moving.
你也一起  卡尔  上车
You too,Carl,take a ride.
跟你说了是在左边第四个货堆里面
I told you,it's the fourth stack on your left.
36排Q区
Q-block,Row 36.
我还是想让你帮我们带路
I'd feel better if you showed us.
我真的应该守在这  斯多克斯先生
I really should stay here,Mr. Stokes.
我还要完成巡逻任务呢
I got to finish my patrol.
为什么  卡尔  你在等人吗
Why,Carl? You expecting somebody?
-没有  -那就上车
- No. - Then get in.
好吧
Okay.
该死
Damn it.
算了吧  杰克
Forget about him,Jack.
他出那扇门时就注定会死
He was dead the minute he stepped out that door.
你我都心知肚明
You and i both know that.
伊桑  我来是想说我很抱歉
Ethan,i just came to say how sorry i am.
出于真心  还是出于礼节
Well,i appreciate the courtesy
我都谢谢你的好意
if not the sincerity.
尽管我觉得我这样做  对我母亲最好
As much as i may feel this is what's best for my mother,
但就我个人而言
On a personal level
我很抱歉让你承受这些
I'm sorry you have to go through this...
还有我不应该在气头上
And for some of the harsher things
对你说那么刻薄的话
I said to you in anger.
恐怕我也要向你道歉
Well,i suppose i owe you an apology,too,
我不该把这次因我错信鲍尔
For accusing you of leaking my role
而铸成大错一事的曝光  怪在你头上
in this Bauer fiasco to the press.
我曾深信你一直在暗算我
I really believed you were trying to blindside me.
鉴于我给你的印象  我倒不觉得奇怪
Considering the impression i gave you,i'm not surprised.
奥利维亚
Olivia,
我是看着你长大的
As someone who's known you most of your life,
给你提点建议吧
I'd like to offer some advice.
请讲
Of course.
在华盛顿  有雄心壮志是优秀品质
Ambition can be a valuable quality here in washington
在生活中也是一样
As well as in life,
但若不加遏制  即便不酿成大错
But unchecked,it can be unhealthy,
也会后患无穷
if not dangerous.
我想说的是
What i'm trying to say is...
你已在总统身边占有一席之地
You got yourself a seat at the president's table.
她听信于你
She listens to you.
但掌管国家政权绝对不像
But running a country is not like running
参加竞选那么简单
A campaign.
其目的不是不惜一切代价获胜
It's not about doing whatever it takes to win.
而是为全体美国人民做出正确的决定
It's about doing what's right for the American people.
有时候二者可以两全其美
Sometimes those things aren't mutually exclusive.
那么
Well...
再见了  奥利维亚
Good-bye,Olivia.
再见
Good-bye.
喂
Hello.
我是奥利维亚
It's Olivia.
你可以报导这件事了  肯  情况有好转
You can go with that story now,ken,and it just got better.
说吧
Tell me.
伊桑·卡宁辞职了
Ethan Kanin's resigning.
为什么
What happened?
我们不是计划好了
I thought the plan was to let him twist
要慢慢折磨他吗
In the wind for a while.
他是被逼之下才出此下策
His hand was forced.
貌似是因为杰克·鲍尔刚杀了迈尔参议员
It seems Jack Bauer just murdered senator Mayer.
你说什么
What?
你不是逗我玩吧
You're kidding me.
还有别人知道这件事吗
Anybody else have this yet?
没有  11点的新闻给你独家报导
not yet.It's all yours in time of the 11 o'clock.
我说过会关照你  没错吧
Told you i'd take care of you,didn't i?
你对我太好了  奥利维亚
You are too good to me,Olivia.
你只管把你答应过的事办好就行
You just hold up your end.
务必让卡宁来背黑锅
Make sure Kanin's the fall guy.
我妈与此毫不相干  明白了吗
My mother is nowhere near this,understand?
没问题
No problem.
她真的不知道你是走露消息的人吗
She really doesn't have any idea that you're the leak?
对  最好别让她知道
No,and it'd better stay that way.
我不会向她透露半个字
She won't hear it from me.
你承诺过的晚餐  想好什么时候了吗
When are we having that dinner you promised?
下周吧
Maybe next week.
你总是推到下周
It's always next week.
去干活吧  还有那个直播要做呢
You'd better get to work if you're going to make that broadcast.
这是初步弹道分析
preliminary  ballistics.
电脑上的这些文件
So these files on the computer--
你认为迈尔被杀前  正在看它们吗
Presumably senator Mayer was looking at 'em before he was killed?
至少有人在看  长官
Someone was,sir.
过去一个小时有人打开看了这些文件
They were opened and viewed within the last hour.
如果说
So if the sen...
参议员是在大厅入口被正面射杀
If the senator was killed point-blank in the entry hall,
为什么门框和栏杆上会有残留的子弹头
how are we explaining the slugs in the door frame and the railing?
还不清楚  长官
I don't know,sir.
让鉴证组的人检查一下
Get the crime lab guys on it.
是  长官
Yes,sir.
沃克探员  拉里·莫斯找你
Agent Walker,it's Larry Moss for you.
请讲
Hello.
迈尔参议员死了
Senator Mayer is dead.
杰克在哪
Where's Jack?
还不知道  我们没有抓住他
Don't know; we don't have him.
好吧  你是不是又认为是杰克干的  拉里
Okay,but what,you think that he did this,Larry?
先杀了伯内特然后又是迈尔吗
First Burnett and now Mayer?
看起来是这样
It looks that way.
什么意思
What do you mean "looks that way"?
这就是我打电话给你的原因
Well,that's why i'm calling. senator Mayer
迈尔是被一支UMP40冲锋枪射杀的
Was killed with a UMP 40 submachine gun.
鲍尔现在在逃  他从哪弄来的这种武器
If bauer was on the run, where'd he get ahold of a weapon like that?
而且现场证据也表明
Also,there's evidence to suggest that the,uh--
迈尔被杀的时候
There was a third party in the house
-有第三方在场  -什么证据
- When the senator was killed. - What kind of evidence?
奇怪的弹痕  被撞坏的法式玻璃门
Unexplained slugs... ...a broken set of french doors,
被挪动的椅子
A chair where it doesn't belong.
也就是说  是别人杀了迈尔
Okay,so are you saying that this third party killed Mayer?
蕾妮  我是想说如果我一开始就
Well,you know,Renee, I might be saying that if i knew what the hell
知道鲍尔在这干嘛就好了
Bauer was doing here in the first place.
好吧  蕾妮  听着
All right,Renee,listen.
我真的想有个折中办法
I want to meet you halfway,i do,
但是  如果你希望我也认为
But if you expect me to even entertain
鲍尔是无辜的  你就要帮帮我呀
Bauer's innocence,you have got to help me here.
不行  拉里  杰克既然仍在暗中调查
I can't,larry. If Jack is still underground,
肯定是有他的原因的
He is underground for a reason.
迈尔的电脑上
There were files open on Mayer's computer--
有打开的关于斯塔克伍德的调查资料
Documents relating to his investigation into starkwood.
你告诉我这个  告诉我这个就行
All right,so just tell me that,tell me that.
鲍尔和你提到过斯塔克伍德吗
Did starkwood ever come up in your conversation with Bauer?
蕾妮
Renee.
我知道  我应该早点相信你
Look,maybe,maybe I should have trusted you before,okay,
但是你现在也要相信我
But you have got to trust me now.
斯塔克伍德到底在扮演什么角色
What role does starkwood play in all this?
陷害鲍尔谋杀了伯内特的人叫约翰·奎恩
The man who framed Jack for burnett's murder was John Quinn,
他是斯达克伍德的一个雇佣兵
a starkwood contractor.
杰克认为他们是朱玛一伙的帮凶
Jack believes that they were behind Juma
也是今天所有恐怖袭击的幕后黑手
And all of the terrorist attacks today.
杰克到迈尔那边取证
He went to Mayer to get the evidence to prove it.
可能奎恩跟踪他到了那里
I have to assume that Quinn followed him there.
我只知道这些  拉里  真的
That's all that I know,Larry,I swear.
好吧  我相信你
Okay,I believe you.
谢谢
Thank you.
你就待在那  我很快会再联络你
Just sit tight,I'll be in touch soon.
让我去帮忙吧   杰克仍在孤军奋战
Well,let me help,Larry. I mean,Jack could still be out there.
他有可能遇到了麻烦
He may be in trouble.
不  我现在还不能放你  还不是时候
No,no,i can't release you,not yet.
瑞斯  怎么样了
Reese,what's the status?
集装箱底盘已准备好了  我马上就过去
Just getting the chassis on,sir,I'll be a minute.
快点
Hurry it up.
稳住  稳住  车还没来
Hold up,hold up,I don't have my truck.
放那  放那  就放那里
Put it down there,i want it there.
米契  上去
Mitch,get up there.
现在开始检测
Let's run a diagnostic now.
瑞斯的拖车一到  马上就走
I want to be ready to roll as soon as Reese gets here with that flatbed.
是  长官
Yes,sir.
好  货在那里
All right,there's the package.
我们应该回到车上
We should get back to the car.
一旦他们行动
We want to be in position
我们就找好位置跟踪集装箱
to follow that container,once they move out.
杰克
Jack.
等一会
Just give me one second.
库柏
Cooper.
是时候给卡尔结账了
Now's as good a time as any to settle up with Carl.
是  长官
Yes,sir.
谢谢  卡尔
Thanks,Carl.
祝你好运
Good luck.
我们走
Let's go.
去哪
Where we going?
钱在卡车里  就隔开一个过道  来吧
Your money's in my truck,just one aisle over.Come on.
杰克  我们该行动了
Jack,we should get going.
不
No.
这是去哪  你不是说  到卡车那拿钱吗
What are you doing? I thought you said the money was in the truck.
你到底要干嘛
What the hell's going on?
往前走
Just keep moving.
听着  我不知道斯多克斯怎么跟你说的
Listen,i don't know what Stokes told you,
我真的从未和别人说过
But I didn't tell a soul.
该死  杰克  你想干什么
Damn it,Jack,what the hell are you doing?
别这么干
Don't do it.
你这么做会把监视任务升级为一场火拼
You're gonna turn a surveillance job into a firefight.
-那会是一个两对十的局面啊  -两对九
- It'll be two against ten. - Two against nine.
就算是  我们也失去了
Right,and we lose our best chance
夺到武器的最佳时机
At getting this weapon.
别坏了你自己的规矩
Don't break your own rules.
你或许救得了一个人
You may save one man,
但那些可能因生化武器
But what about the thousands of people
而死去的成千上万的人怎么办
Who could die in a biological attack?
是你的承诺重要还是他们的命重要
Is this about you,Jack,or about them?
你想阻止一场灾难  还是想让它发生
You want to prevent another disaster or ensure that it's going to happen?
够远了
That's far enough.
转过去
Turn around.
你要杀我
You're going to kill me,
就得正视着我的眼睛开枪
You're going to have to look me in the eye.
好吧
Okay.
该死
Damn it.
谢谢  谢谢
Thank you,thank you.
在他们发现之前
We've got about 30 seconds
我们还有30秒时间
Before they figure out what happened.
我们的备用计划呢
Okay,what's our fallback?
-偷卡车  -硬来吗
- Steal the truck.  - Strong?
我负责正面强攻  你从东侧掩护我
I'll make the direct assault,you cover the east flank.
我们只需要狠狠地干上一场
All we need is a big enough firefight
好让我们中的一个混上车  准备好了吗
To get one of us behind the wheel. You ready?
-是的  -行动
- Yeah. - Go.
怎么样了
How do we look?
检测完毕  长官
Diagnostics check out,sir.
一切正常
The package is stable.
好
Good.
把货装上车
All right,let's get her on the chassis!
库柏  快点  我们出发了
Cooper,come on. Let's roll.
库柏  收到没
Cooper,do you copy?
多伦
Dolen.
检查下隔壁的通道  把库柏找出来
Check the next aisle over. Find cooper.
待在那
Hold your position.
等我信号
Wait for my signal.
库柏死了  库柏死了
Cooper's down,cooper's down.
警报  警报
Go red,go red!
快走  格里尔
Let's move out... greer.
打  打
Engage... engage.
瑞斯  快把车开走
Reese,get the truck out of here now!
上  上  上
Go,go,go!
托尼
Tony!
我去追卡车
The truck-- i'm going after it.
-掩护我  -好的
- Cover me now! - All right.
两个枪手  呈扇形展开  找出他们
Two shooters-- fan out and find them.
托尼  我是杰克  能听到吗
Tony,this is Jack-- do you copy?
放下武器
Drop it.
托尼
Tony?
我认识你
I know you.
你是爱默生的人
You're on emerson's crew.
-你是阿尔梅达  对吧  -该死
- You're almeida,right?  - Damn it!
我知道鲍尔和你在一起  他在哪
I know Bauer's with you. Now,where is he?
-我是拉里·莫斯  -拉里  我是杰克
- Larry Moss  - Larry,it's Jack.
杰克  你死哪里去了
Jack,where the hell have you been?
你马上紧急调派多职能小队过来
I need you to scramble multiple teams
在236高速的29号出口的车辆称重站那
To a weigh station on highway 236,exit 29.
我在南边10英里的一辆大拖车上
I'm in a big rig about ten miles south.
出什么事了
What's going on?
你还得派疾病控制中心的人来
You also need to send a CDC recovery unit.
为什么
Why?
我这有在亚历山大港截获的生化武器
I'm in possession of a biological weapon interdicted at the port of alexandria.
生化武器
A biological weapon?
拉里  听我说
Larry,just listen to me.
我不在乎你是否要抓我
I don't care if you arrest me.
也不在乎你是否要杀我
I don't care if you shoot me.
只管把你的人派过来就是了
Just get your teams out here.
估计敌人会尾随而来
I fully expect to be pursued by hostiles.
是斯塔克伍德的人吗
Starkwood?
你怎么知道斯塔克伍德的
How do you know about starkwood?
我和蕾妮谈过
I talked to Renee.
我在迈尔的电脑上也看到了
And i saw what was on mayer's computer.
拉里  他们是冲着武器来的
Larry,they're coming after this weapon.
绝没有错的
You can count on it.
注意  我相信  托尼已成了人质
Now,be advised,i believe that Tony Almeida is being held hostage.
好  我会发出部门预警的
All right,i'll call out an inter-agency alert.
我们会从两处双管齐下
We'll secure both locations.
拉里  快点
Larry,hurry.
该死
Damn it!
长官  我是斯多克斯
Sir,this is Stokes.
你那边情况如何
What's your status?
武器到手了  我们在返回途中
The package is secure-- we're inbound.
鲍尔呢
What about bauer?
他在现场  长官
He's at the scene,sir,
但他躲到了附近的掩体
But he sought cover nearby.
我们得假定他通知了当局
Well,we have to assume that he contacted the authorities,
我们要加快进度了
So we better be on an accelerated timetable.
快过来
Get over here.
10分钟内   我们随后就到
It will be there in ten minutes. We're right behind.
我这边有地面部队迎接你归来
I've got teams on the ground prepping for your arrival.
拉里·莫斯
Larry Moss.
拉里  这是杰克
Larry,it's jack.
我还在236高速上
I'm still on route 236,
但我被迫在离车辆秤重站
But i had to stop approximately seven miles
约7英里处停下来了
Before the weigh station.
杰克  有两队人马正向你处赶去
Jack,i got two units moving to you right now.
你得重新部署他们
Yeah,well,you're gonna have to redirect them.
斯塔克伍德重新夺回了生化武器
Starkwood reacquired the bioweapon.
他们弄到了码头的货运直升机
They managed to access one of the dock's freight helicopters.
他们火力压制住我  把武器空运走了
While they had me pinned down,they airlifted the freight right out of here.
他们从我这位置往正西方走了
They were headed due west from my current position.
西边  那里有一处他们的大型军用设施
West... they got a large military facility In that area.
好  把他们重新部署到那去
Okay,good-- redirect the teams there.
杰克  我不能攻击私人领地
Jack,i can't assault a private compound
除非我有他们持有生化武器的证据
Unless i have proof that a weapon exists.
好吧  疾病控制中心的人呢
Okay,where's the CDC?
他们在紧急召集一队人马
They're scrambling a team right now.
把他们派到我这来
Send them to me.
这有你要的证据
You'll have all the proof you need.
杰克  发生什么事了
Jack,what happened?
在截获过程中  有一瓶泄露了
One of the canisters was breached during the interdiction.
一些生物剂释放了出来
Some of the bio-agent was released.
我
I...
我暴露其中了
I was exposed.
杰克  待在那里别动
Okay. Jack,just sit tight.
疾病控制中心的人上路了
CDC's on the way.
他们马上就到
They're going to be there soon.